Friends, it's my birthday, and the name is written for
Rakhi Didi, Dramabaaz Rakhi.
Yes, actually I am everyone's favourite.
And Payal Don, now I am excited about the
gifts given by my subscribers
which I have not opened yet.
Soldiers, don't lose courage.
[screaming sound] Hold your breath.  Finally
friends, the rain stopped.  It was raining heavily continuously for two days.
By the way,
trespassing is still happening.
Not trespassing.
Light drizzle.  And you can see,
friends, the flowers that are from my birthday.
How cute she is.   It's
exactly like this.
Rotten.
You can just call it a gift.  Hey, let's open the gift
Anshu Bhai.  Friends, I have
not opened my birthday gifts yet.   He
made my birthday very nice.  I do
n't know where did he get so much intelligence from
?  What did you eat?  What did you
plan to eat to celebrate my birthday
?
How many almonds did I have?
By eating almonds one by one, my sister can
become so intelligent that she can make my birthday so
wonderful.  So think
what will happen if you eat four almonds?  It will be made without intelligence.  It will
burst.   I will
finish it without it.  I do
n't eat because I ate four almonds.  Guys, I
also
got a lot of gifts [music] from my lovely subscribers.  Which I have
not seen.  I have seen what he gave me.
And there are still some gifts that I have
n't seen.  They are very big and very
good.  I'm so excited to see them [in music].
Okay
Anshu let's go.   I have a
higher score than you.
Look friends,
my platoon is coming on the muddy road.  And what is this in their hands
?
This is a gift.
He could not give you a gift on your birthday.   Are.  He is
bringing me birthday gifts.
What's up friends?  Payal has a
blue box in her hand and the silent girl has a
red box in her hand.
Dabba Dabba Chubba
come come come come anyway today I am going to
open my birthday gift I am feeling so
happy as Anshu asked me what will you take, by the way
why are you feeling so happy, I want to
see it, if I
like it then I will take it too
Ram Ram
Ram Ram Bhaiya Ram Ram Ram Ram
Bhaiya Ram Ram Hey hey
you show me what have you brought, I am
not showing you the whole thing,
why did you not give it to me on my birthday, I am
giving it to you now, what gold did he
not give it to me on my birthday, it remained
my diamond only.  No,
why didn't you give it to me on my birthday
?
I had forgotten.
Okay, take it.   She
forgot to give me a birthday gift on my birthday.
Hey friends, what's the matter?  They
forget to give gifts on the birthday itself.  That means
buy gifts only for the birthday and then
forget to give them on the birthday itself.   I had
forgotten home.
Mine was left at home.  You also forgot.
Friends, these are some gifts that my
cute subscribers came to my house to give me.
Even though I hadn't met him.  So
I am very excited to open these.  I arrange all
my gifts on the table.  Come on
friends, the light has gone off as I have
kept these gifts and these are all my birthday
gifts which I got on my birthday, I
mean not all of them, some gifts were
finished after the birthday itself, I mean they were meant for eating and
drinking, so
whose gift should I open first,
my brother, your friend, this is a complete Lego
box, by the time I open this my next
birthday will come [laughs]
Bhaiya, I will be 26 years old
[nasal sound]
don't tell me my age, okay, do
n't show off your status by telling my age, I am
5 years old, I am just
six years old, yes, then tell me whose gift should I
open first?  Look, I haven't seen these two
yet.  So Silent Girl's or this one?   Of the
silent girl.  Hey, open this one first and
get it voted.
Its its its its its its its
[laughs] because I always walk backwards.
Come brother, this Fortuner was given by aunty.
Yes, I
made this lid and brought it.
[screaming]
Wow, there are so many gifts in this.
Anchor angel come on.
Come what is happening, sit there, there the
lady has come here,
a lot of work is going on in the pandal,
sit in the paltan, I have brought a dholak to play,
hey, I saw some gifts in it,
hey there is a light also, I saw the face of a lizard in it, go ahead,
friends, our Payal Don has
made a very aesthetic gift for me, so I am
very excited to leave it, she has
learnt from me to make it aesthetic, this
bad habit of taking credit everywhere,
my dream car will expose this box
and
oh hey hey hey hey
friends, this is Payal.
Wow,
this is an owl, this is Amit Bhaiya.
Same Amit Bhaiya,
this is Payal.  Payal is the real owl.  Oh
friend, I have received a lot of these gifts
this time.  I had a lot of fun friends.  I have got a
lot of these metallic toys.
She has brought me the bike.  Brother, can I
tell you something interesting?
I did not tell all this.
He doesn't develop these habits like government employees, friend.  Have you made a
hand pump to take credit for everything or have our government
made two of them?  Seeing this, that meme came to my mind.
Many leaders come to give bananas to a patient.  They
give a banana and everyone touches it like this.
Oh, it's gone.   The
light is on in it.  Hey, it also opens from the front,
look like this.
How?   From
here.
Hey, it opens brother.  Look at this.   Is it
open?  Thank you so much Payal Don
for such a nice bike.  I will
always take care of this Payal Don.  I have got this statue of Payal Don.
Oh, take the
don thing, it
really hits you, this is a punch,
this is a punch, friends, let me show you how to hit it, it is
in his nose, friends, this is my sister, this one
is green and this one is sitting blue today
[laughs] she
ate the lizard, yuck, what else is there in it, it got
scratched and this one
is a panda, sweet little panda, hey, what is this,
this empty Pringles can?
Brother, I had eaten it.
[laughs] You couldn't wait for two days, did you?
So after two days you are going to give me a gift.
Friends, I couldn't wait for two days.   She
ate the spring and that too, she
brought such small ones and you ate them too.
[laughs] Ever since
I saw that box, I've been saying I'm going to
open it and eat it as soon as possible.
I was thinking the same.
Friends, what is this?
Panda.
Panda.  This is an eraser.  I don't do this work with pencil.
This is an eraser.
Yes, this is an eraser.  Diet Coke is very much
in trend.  I will drink it after cooling it.  Alcohol.   I will
quietly keep it behind.  Otherwise its destiny is
fixed [music] on this.
By the way, I had brought two.  I drank one.
So why have you brought me a gift?
Brother [laughs]
what should I do then?   She is
so hot, so hungry.
Whatever food and drink she brought for me, she ate it herself.
Brother, its last gift is in front of me.  It's ahead of you.
Wow friends, Payal has brought Don for me.
Glasses with cataracts.   I'm
liking it.  I'm liking it.
I am absolutely shaking Vijay Deverakonda.  Only
Rasmika will not be available.
What?
Only Rasmika will not be available.  You will get more beautiful than that.   In
this way, I make myself happy by making my friends happy.
And friends, lastly these are
cute stickers.  Thank you so much
Payal Don.
Those which have no use.
Those who are ok.
No use brother, I will put it on my diary.
And what is this crazy thing?   I will put it on the
phone.  I will install it on the laptop.
Brother.
Yes.
This is Payal.  No more.  [laughter] Here you go.
Keep it aside.  It would have been better if you had given it on my birthday.
Silent girl,
show me your gifts.  What have you brought?
Friends, it seems this is a box of sweets.   It
is red.  The entire box is red.   I
brought watermelon in it.
Tear it apart brother.  Tear it.
Why are you tearing up?   That
's right friends.  I will
unbox mine myself.  Oh oh hey stop.
Brother, let me open up too.
Friends, I am really excited to open the gifts.   Isn't it
?
Hot Wheels box.  [screaming] There are
two Hot Wheels and what are the rest of them
?   There are
not two.  There will be more.  Where did you
open the box and see it?  The box is torn.
She has already torn the box.  Hey
friends, she has brought the material to build a bridge.   I will
build such a flyover which will not get washed away in a single water.
We will build such a flyover that it will cut straight from here to
Bhabhi.
Thank you silent Anamika.  Thank you so much
for giving this gift.  Now friends,
I will play full bridge at home.  So now we
will unbox the Rakhi gift which you all have
already seen.  So let me quickly
show you what all he gave me.  So
friends, this is what it gave me.
This is brother's face.  This is brother's.
Correct.  It's your face.  The biggest
gift that Rakhi has given me is this
Meta AI, it looks
so strong brother.  Meaning,
my heart became a garden.  I was
thinking of buying these and he bought them for me.
I take it like this.
This is pretty cool, friends.  Very much.
See the photo from here with one click,
all your photos have been clicked and are directly
imported into my phone.
All of you are fine.  Yes [laughs]
take my picture,
shut up, a
photo of an animal has been added to my phone
and it has very good speakers which produce
very good sound and the rest of the
friends, these are amazing and I will
say to it, hey son,
hey Meta, prove that my sister is a human being,
Meta is saying that this is unacceptable
[laughs]
he has said this thing to you, okay,
any unusual habits, mind, it is true, Meta is saying that
your sister has so many unusual
habits.  So she can't be proven as a human being.
Ok?  Now let's keep it.  And the
second most dangerous gift that
he has given me is
yes, how is this watch?  G Shock
G Shock and I forgot the name of it the whole man.
What was it?
G Shock
GD 200 I know it has Bluetooth.  It
connects to my phone.  Whatever
notifications or calls come, all the
notifications appear on top.
Brother, I know it.
This is a very strong watch.  Very sturdy, [music]
I'll wear this right now.  And the third
gift that I found more dangerous is this.  Oh wow!   The
angel knows a lot.
These are New Balance shoes which I
wanted to buy but friends, I do
n't buy them after looking at the price.  I have a
very bad habit.  I can't buy things for myself.
Not for me.  [sound of clearing throat]
I'll buy it for you guys.  Ok
?  I can buy any expensive thing for them.
But for myself, I
think a thousand times before buying anything.  A thousand
times.
That's why I get it for brother without thinking even once.
Yes, take these also.
I have a lot of heart.
Ok.  Your garland will be made from these.  If
you score less marks this time, then
this time he will bring Harwari.   It was
sad and it hit a nerve.   There will be
no discussion about this and he
gave me his toothbrush.
This is brother's toothpaste, sugarcane brush.
This is very useful for brother in the morning.
This is to clean your mouth.  What else did
you give me?  What else?
I gave this many monsters.
He had given a lot of monsters in it.
Many of which friends drank.  He drank it.   He
finished it all.
And in this life I have
not drunk a single monster.  He
drank the whole monster.
Now I will take this also.
Yes, take this also.  very nice.
I also gave you life.
You take this and I will bring whatever
you are going to bring.
What should I bring?
What are you going to bring?  [laughter]
Friends, our fine fellow is about to give us a very
big surprise.  I will bring your
surprise.  Ok?   No. No.
Yes.
No, take it now.
Hey, no problem, take it away, take it away.
Brother keep
it.  Keep it.  Keep it.  Keep it.
What is it?
That will be known.  That is a
big surprise for everyone.  Ok
?
You will know in a week or two.
This is going to give a big surprise in a week or two.   I did
this too, sister.
Yes.  And he has given a silver chain to his friends.
He has given me a total of 25 gifts.
And I could not give even 25 gifts.
That's why I will give it to him right now.
Bring it.
Why?  And look below this, here it is.
Where did it go?
Hey darling, here it is.
What is in it?
Evil came into it.
As if you are under evil eye.  This is for the thing that most often affects your channel.   Thank
you.  I wore it around my neck.  No, I will
make you wear it on your ear.
Ok.
So friends, my sister has given me an evil eye.
So that I am not affected by evil eye.  Thank
you so much.
I will wear this.  I need it, I need it.
And if she wears such big earrings, and
friends, he gave me this car.
And I brought it for my own benefit
because I like it very much.
Okay, and let me keep this coffee dead off here.
And
how much did this Jaguar perfume cost?
Tell me this correctly.
He had come.  I don't know how much it cost.  This
wallet.
Yes, he gave me this wallet.  Thank you.   What
else was there?
And friends, he had given me these socks to paint.
Yes, this biscuit was with me and my brother for a long time.
Demand.
Yes.   He gave
me these socks.  What else was there?
I gave you a time machine.  [laughs]
With this, I will travel to my future friends
and tell them that this is what
my brother looks like at night.
This is you.
And
I also gave you these books and copies for your studies.  He has also given me a copy and pen,
friends,
I had actually brought this diary for myself
and wearing this
our Tony Bhaiya got upset,
Iron Man
and friends he has also given me two shirts which
I wore so many times and made them fragrant,
show it to me too,
yes and friends he had given me this dinosaur,
yes because it is exactly like Bhaiya, look, he gave me a
phone cover,
friends he gave me a phone cover worth Rs
which I will not wear at all because
these covers stick to the pocket.   I hit him, this is
not original,
this is original, I have brought it for 2 lakhs and the
rest of the gifts were finished hand to hand,
like cake, Woke and Coke,
oh cake [laughs] cake
and what is its shape, if it was
not a cake then
I had kept the cake, the cake was from
all of us, it was not from his side,
oh cake,
you take credit for everyone, brother, you are becoming the government,
friends, Tony Bhaiya aka
Iron Man and this Mercedes AMG was
given to me by my best friend, Sumit Bhai, who is
also my manager.  And yes, now I am
excited about the gifts given by my subscribers
which I have
not opened yet.  So let's see
this, friends, it's my birthday and its
name is written for Rakhi Didi, Dramabaaz
Rakhi,
actually I am everyone's favourite, oh will there
definitely be a frame in it,
Rakhi
frame frame frame
frame
photo frame,
yes it
seems like it will turn on the light, yes yes let me try
lighting
it,
oh it does burn, my
photo is appearing in it.
Friends, its photo is looking dirty in this.
I thought, friend, it will burn while charging.
Yes.
This is actually mine, that's why I
shine everywhere, that's why it is shining even without life.
[MUSIC]
And
yes, great fun.
I called you a fetter.  [laughter]
And let's open this gift.  Hey
brother, my name is written on this.  And Payal
Don Payal stop stop.  Hey stop.
Friends, some subscriber has
given a gift in the name of all of us.  And Shivanshu Bhaiya, my
point turned out to be funny, we will see it later.
The Romer Amit Group Yo Romer Amit
Group First friends let me see my gift
what is in it?   Are you
coming?
Brother, it looks strong to me.  Which car
is it?
Look at it.  I have told everyone
that that brother wants such a gift, that is why everyone has
given such a gift.
Friends, I have enough metallic cars.  It was
fun.
Say thank you to the person from whom you learnt this as soon as possible.
Thank you so much brother for giving me such a lovely
gift.  Look friends, what a
beautiful car it looks like.  What a beautiful
toy.  Hey, how big is it?  Hey, this
frame also comes out.  Wow friends, she
looks so beautiful.  What a beautiful
toy.
Brother, this looks really nice.
Its gate was opened.
Open the next one also.  Bonnet
bonnet
sounds from inside?
Yes and the
light came on, light, look quickly, quickly,
hey oh oh,
this will work,
friends, you have given me a really fun toy, thank
you so much brother, whoever has given me this toy,
why are you breaking it, hey, I am
taking out its frame, I will
take out its vehicle,
yes
stop,
friends, one of my subscribers has
also given me this gun.  Why are you scared
?  Look,
one of these also comes out, this is an
automatic pistol, yes this is Shivanshu's
gift, Shivanshu ji's
perfume,
friends, someone has given a perfume to our decent guy
on my birthday, it smells
very bad, does it smell bad
because you sit next to me, right, no
Bhaiya, they know that Shanshu Bhaiya smells very bad,
F also smells bad, that's why they have
given it to him,
okay, so
maybe Prasad, you also sit next to it.
She is also sitting next to me.
Your work is done perfume ahead then.   Isn't it
?  [screaming sound]
Because friends, our pile don't take bath.
Yes, I have come after taking bath.  Ok.  I take a bath daily.
Ask Amit Bhaiya if she will not take bath.
I take a bath first.
Yes, I swear to God.
I took a bath first.
Now he will say that I have taken bath yesterday.
Yes, I am sitting after taking bath yesterday.  This
is the next gift.  Payal Don.   I
will open it.
The photo will be the same in this also.   There
is a photo frame in this also.
Bhaiya,
this will be the dirtiest photo of Payal.  Hey
what, hey wow,
this doesn't work straight away.
I told you that only what shines shines.
But there are two photos of Payal in it.   These are
photos of Jodhpur and Jaisalmer.
Yes, there are two more.
I am bringing it to burn.
See you later, I will open more gifts.
It has those play buttons.
Play button
play button
Hrithik.  Well, this is that one, friends.
Friends, this is my subscriber
who had a heart operation and he
lives near my village.  This is a
congratulations of Rs 10 million which he gave me on
my birthday.  These
friends for Romer Amit Group
oh how good I am looking.  I
look so good.
Everyone looks beautiful.   The
most beautiful thing in this is the green grass.
So friends, keep looking at their light white.
Now let's look at the next gifts.   Is there
anything left?  Hey, this was also given to me by my cute
subscriber brother.  This handkerchief is for this one
, for this one and
for this one, these three are Fefi.  All
three of them keep having noses [laughs].
Brother
and it has perfume in it. Hey watch friends, it is a
heavy watch.  Give me your hand.
Heavy is dangerous.
This one is also a gift, it burns.  It's burnt, it's
burnt.
Oh, hey, it's burnt.  It's burnt, it's burnt.
Friends, there is a statue of Mata Rani ji in it.
Friends, this art and craft gift was
given to Himanshi Chidiya by her sister.
Learn something from him.  How talented is she?
You don't learn anything, don't tell her about me,
see friends
what I have made, happy birthday bhaiya and it has also been written
about some important people of my life,
bhaiya, I have not written about me, I have not
written about you, I have just given my heart,
who made this ghost,
Palak
friends, Palak has given me its face
because she had another very good painting, that one got
spoiled because of the rain,
yes it got spoiled in the rain and Palak has
also given me this cup, brother's birthday,
brother's birthday,
happy birthday,
but now sister's birthday is coming.
[screaming] Get the
party ready.   Will
you guys give it to me?
So friends, I got some
lovely gifts on my birthday.  The
greatest, look, this is kept [Music]
Where has Punia gone?
I forgot about Punia.  Punia had
come.  Where did Punia go?
That emergency call had come so she would go.
At the shop,
yes
Punia friends, he is a very hardworking boy.  I will touch it.
Yes, it will open like this.  Such a car will be made and
we removed the lid of it, removed the lid, this is the
McLaren, I have got three such big boxes and two
such thick booklets,
read them from them and
I will make it,
this is a packet, oh the packet should not be misplaced, the
packet should not be misplaced, so friends, I got some
such lovely gifts on my
birthday, seeing them my heart was filled with joy, I
enjoyed it a lot
and thank you very much to all of you too, you all
gave me so many wishes on my birthday,
you have been giving me so much love till now,
thank you very much for all that too.  Just
keep showering your love like this always.  Thank you so much.
I love you so much friends, all of you.
Friends, once upon a time this room used to be mine.
But now it has taken over my sweet
room.  And she keeps partying in it with her women's society.  She keeps
enjoying.
And friends, I no
longer have any place to live.  There is no place
left.  Let me tell you one thing, when brother is not
in this room, this room remains absolutely clean and
very nice.  If we come here it
becomes dirty.  Look
friends, these three girls have snatched my room from
me.   The
dirtiest thing is brother's clothes,
oh that's not the point.  That is not the point,
I am saying something else.  You are saying something else.
I am telling you friends that he has taken away my
place to live.  I have nothing
left to live for now.  I don't have a place to stay.
What happened?
Tell me what is the matter?   The
matter is that this room used to be mine.
Is it or not?  But now he has taken over this room.
So, do you know how he got it
confiscated then?  Yes.
Just like a dog asks before sitting,
how did he make brother move?
Yes.  Friends, she slowly came into my room
, and then she collected all her stuff
in my room.  Now I have nothing
left.   So
now I have only one option left that I will
build a new studio for myself, separate on the terrace.
Ok.
Brother, I was in your party, right?
So who is letting you live there?
Friends, I will build a big rooftop studio
very soon.  What is this?
Cancelled.
Party cancelled.
Rakhi's Rakhi's Rakhi's Rakhi
caught it just like that, brother, it's not ours,
see friends, Payal
is teaching self-defense techniques to Pari by becoming a grand master,
look, look, she is teaching how to break hands,
training is going on, training, training,
friends, for two days, not even 1% of sunshine has been seen, it's
raining nicely and we are having a lot of
fun, so
what do you all want in the party, cow dung,
gevar, pav, gevar,
gevar, he is
right, friends, I feel like eating gevar,
but I have given up sugar, no
problem brother, there is no sugar power for gevar,
today I will cheat, a little bit of gevar, gevar, gevar is gevar,
not
gevar, one of the years,
friends, my head started itching after
hearing the name of Ghevar,
friends, I have been feeling like eating it for the last 10 days, I am not
able to eat it, but
I don't like it, more
people are going to eat Ghevar, who knows, what will we get to know about the
taste of Ghevar,
today we will eat a little bit of Ghevar,
friends, I will ask one of my dieticians, can
I eat Ghevar  Am?
Oh and I know the dietician,
I will come back after eating the entire 250 gram packet.
Friends, we have come to our all time favourite
Haldiram.  And what is this, this is being made.   It
seems another floor is being added for us
because we come here a lot friends.
And who will eat what from here
?
Pav Bhaji.
Will eat gevar.  We have come to eat gevar.  Pav
Bhaji.  Friends, Haldiram's Pav Bhaji is everyone's favourite.
Wow friends,
how beautiful the gevar looks.  But I can't
eat.
Eat brother, eat it, I am fed up.  Hey, are
n't you eating all this at once?
No, I am sugar free.
Well, I refused.  I
refused to do anything with my diet.  [Music] Vada pav with
hot tea.  Ok.
Eat it, eat it.
Friends, everyone's eating and drinking was over.
This tea of ​​mine is left.  My Vada
Pav has not arrived yet.  Everyone ate it and
everyone liked the ads too.  I am just looking at
how to become a favor.
Friends, it seems I will not be able to have Vada Pav in this life.
Hey uncle [music] friend, your tea has also gone
cold.  Tea and bread.
Friends, my tea also got cold but pav
sorry vada pav vada pav vada
pav did not come.
Finally friends, Vada Pav has arrived.  Wow, thank
you so much brother.
Check its smell.
So the fragrance will be checked even from inside the paper.
Do it, don't check it, do it.  Do it, do it.  Hey, do it.
[laughter] If you have
any requests, let me know.
I should refuse right now.
Correct.
Well, I started
thinking.  [laughter]
Let's get in the car.  Come on
soldiers, don't lose courage.  Keep your breath crying.
We lost.  Lost.  Lost.
Brother, brother,
brother, save me.
friend to whom?  So
who can't breathe?
I will
not be able to breathe at all.
This dosa is for you and
ice cream is also for you.
Hey friend,
this is the mango one.
This is the mango one.
Very good.
And this is the paan seller.  Here mom, there is a paan for you.   Did
you eat the paan one or the mango one?
Will you eat the mango one or the paan one?
Aunty doesn't like mango.
You don't like mango?
Yes.  This is the paan seller.  Kulfi
is from Paan.
Eat whatever you want to eat.  So
friends, let's end this video now
and tell me in the comments what you thought was the
best thing that I got as a gift.
Hey, why are you fighting unnecessarily?
Hey, are you feeling like
fighting more? Hey, are you feeling like
fighting more?  If you want to fight,
come to the back field and fight.  Come on, what's the
matter?  Yes, so friends, it is okay for you to tell me in the comments what
you liked the most
?  And until then, be alert
friends.  Keep watching The Roma Channel,
like, share and subscribe.
Me too, brother too.  Bye bye, if you
break it, he will kill you.
Give [screaming voice]
Give
quickly, give quickly Payal, quickly,
quickly
Payal, what are you thinking?
Move quickly, it's useless Payal, move away